samys.com 2019-05-28

# Samy's Camera: Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy

* * *

At Samy's Camera, we value your privacy and personal security. Our privacy commitment is described in this Privacy Policy. As our services evolve and we perceive the need or desirability of using information collected in other ways, we may from time to time amend this Privacy Policy. We post the effective date of our Privacy Policy on our website ("Site"). We encourage you to check our Site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect and any changes that may have been made to them. If we make material changes to this Policy we will post the revised Policy and the revised effective date on this Site. Please check back here periodically or contact us at the address listed at the end of this Policy. 

This Policy is part of our Terms of Use Agreement. Please click here to see that Agreement. 

**Anonymous User Information - Cookies**

In general, you can visit samys.com without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself. However, as you browse our Site, our web servers record data on your visit, using cookies and other tracking technology. A cookie is a small file that is stored on your computer that identifies it specifically with our Site, allowing us to simplify the login and checkout processes. This information also allows us to analyze what our visitors are looking for, whether or not they find it, and how they work with our Site. Some cookies are deleted once you leave our Site ("session cookies"), while other cookies remain after your leave our site ("persistent cookies") so that you are recognized when you return to the Site. None of the information collected by these methods in any way contains personal details about you or any of our other users - it is strictly statistical information about your computer and internet connection. You can set your browser to refuse cookies, but doing so will limit system performance and may even cause certain features of the Site to malfunction or not to work at all. 

**Information You Provide and How We Use It**

 _Purchases_

. If you make an online purchase with us at Samy's Camera, we require personal information to complete the order. This includes name, address, credit card, billing, shipping, and other contact information that you provide. All of this information is maintained on our servers. 

_My Account_

. You may save your personal information by creating an account on our Site. If you choose to do so we may collect your name, credit card information, billing and shipping address and other information you choose to submit. You may be asked to provide a log-in or user name and to select a password that will be used to access your account information. 

_Email or Other Registration_

. If you register to receive our newsletters we will collect your email address. If you send us an email we may retain your email address. We may use the information you provide to contact you, to respond to inquiries or to provide information about our products or services to you. You may unsubscribe or change your email address for email promotions at any time by following the instructions mentioned prominently within each email promotion. 

_Promotions_

. If you register on the site or participate in an activity or promotion on the site, you may be required to provide certain information and to certify that you meet the requirements, including age, for participation.

 _Job Applications._

Prospective employees may submit information to apply for employment with Samy's Camera by visiting the Employment Opportunities page, where we list open positions. Resumes may be sent by email by clicking the links on this page or may be faxed to us at the number below. Please be aware that emails are not secure, so do not send sensitive information to us in an email.

 _Comments or other Posts_

. If you post a comment or other material to our Site it can be viewed by the general public. Any information or comment that you post to our Site must comply with our Terms of Use.

By providing personal information through this site you explicitly agree to our collection and use of all such information as described in this Privacy Policy. You agree that we may use the personal information you provide to respond to your inquiries, process orders, contact you regarding customer service, let you know about products or services which may be of interest to you or to personalize our service to meet your needs or preferences. You also agree that we may share your personal information with our affiliated companies and third parties as described in this Privacy Policy. You further agree that the information you provide is current, accurate and complete and that you will update it if there are any changes.

**Disclosure of Your Information**

We will never sell or give your personal information to marketers or solicitors. We may disclose your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties if: (1) you request or authorize it; (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you; (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our Terms of Use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety or the rights, property or safety of our users or others (e.g., to a consumer reporting agency for fraud protection etc.); (4) the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of services or assets (e.g., in the event that substantially all of our assets are acquired by another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets); (5) the information is provided to our agents, outside vendors or service providers to perform functions on our behalf (e.g., analyzing data, providing information verification for fraud prevention, providing marketing assistance, providing customer service, processing orders, etc.); or (6) to others as described in this Privacy Policy.

**Protecting Children**

Because of the nature of our business, our products and services are not designed to appeal to minors, and therefore we do not knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children under 18. If we have reason to believe that information is being provided by a person under the age of 18 we will not collect the information.

**Opt-Out, Access, and Security**

You may, at any time, update, make changes or corrections to your My Account or preferences, or delete them, simply by visiting the My Account page of the Site after providing your log-in name and password and clicking on My Account. You may also direct us to change or delete your information by fax, mail or email at the addresses and numbers provided below. You can direct us to delete your email address from our mailing list simply by following the instructions on any email you receive. We will act on your instructions promptly, but making changes or deleting information may take two weeks or more to become effective. We will honor any requests for us to provide or change information when your log-on information and password are used.

Our Site uses SSL (Secure Sockets Layer) security technology to encrypt information you provide to us through the Site, but any information you provide us by email is unencrypted. SSL is an industry-standard protocol for encryption over the internet. Data transmission over the internet is never 100% secure.

While we take steps to protect your personal information and keep it secure, you also play a role in protecting your information. You can help to maintain the security of your online transactions by not sharing your log-in name or password with anyone. If we receive instructions using your log-in information and password we will assume that the instructions have been authorized by you. Samy's Camera cannot guaranty the security of any information you transmit to us or from our Site, and therefore you use our site at your own risk.

We may maintain customer information in both electronic and paper format at our company offices, including our office in Los Angeles, California. All electronic information is processed and maintained in California.

**Inapplicability of Privacy Policies of any Linked Sites or Other Parties** ****

Our Site may contain links to other sites such as our affiliates and third parties. This Privacy Policy only addresses Samy's Camera's use and disclosure of your information collected on this Site, if any. While we try to link only to sites that share our standards and respect for privacy, we are not responsible for the privacy practices of any third parties or the content of linked sites, although we do encourage you to read the applicable privacy policies and terms and conditions of such parties or web sites.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy** ****

We will occasionally amend this Privacy Policy to reflect company and customer feedback and we reserve the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy at any time. The use of your information is subject to the Privacy Policy and Terms of Use in effect at the time of use. The provisions contained in this Privacy Policy supersede all previous notices or policies regarding our privacy practices with respect to this site. We post the effective date of our Privacy Policy on our site. We encourage you to check our site frequently to see the current Privacy Policy to be informed of how Samy's Camera is committed to protecting your information and providing you with improved content on our website in order to enhance your online experience. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy we will post the revised Privacy Policy and the revised effective date on this site.

**Your Comments are Appreciated** ****

If you have any questions or comments regarding our Privacy Policy or our website, you can contact us at Samy's Camera 12636 Beatrice St. Los Angeles, CA 90066, by phone at (310) 591-2100, by fax at (310) 591-2120 or by email at [info@samys.com](mailto:info@samys.com). This site is owned and operated by Samy's Camera, Inc., which controls any information submitted through this site.

Effective Date: As of January 31st, 2012  
© 2019 by Samy's Camera, Inc. All rights reserved.
